thetracktor.com 2017-03-27

# The Tracktor - Amazon Price Tracker

### Privacy Policy

The Tracktor takes personal privacy very seriously. Our privacy policy is simple. The Tracktor will not provide, rent, or make available in any way, any contact information of our users to any other parties. Period.

To specifically address concerns of our users, we ensure the following: 

  * Customer e-mail addresses are used solely for price notifications and if desired, our newsletter. 
  * All user information is stored in a secure data environment.
  * No personally identifiable information is collected on visitors to this site.

##### Cookies and Web Beacons

The Tracktor collects anonymous data from the use of our product. This information may be used by third parties for targeted advertising purposes. We use "Google Analytics" to collect information about use of this site. Google Analytics collects information such as how often users visit this site, what pages they visit when they do so, user demographic and interests, and what other sites they used prior to coming to this site. We use the information we get from Google Analytics only to improve this site. Google's ability to use and share information collected by Google Analytics about your visits to this site is restricted by the Google Analytics Terms of Use (as amended for government websites) and the Google Privacy Policy. You can prevent Google Analytics from recognizing you on return visits to this site by disabling cookies on your browser.

We and the third parties we authorize may receive and store certain types of non-personally identifiable information whenever you interact with us by using “cookies,” “web beacons” and analogous technology. “Cookies” are small files that are placed on your computer or your internet browser memory to enable the owner of the cookie to recognize your browser and to provide convenience and other features to you. It is important to note that the cookies that we use, or permit others to use, do not contain and are not tied to personally-identifiable information about you.

You may be able to direct your internet browser not to allow cookies and you can typically delete existing cookies from your computer at any time. Please note, however, if you set such browser settings or delete existing cookies then some elements of our website may not function properly or be available to you. 

##### Preference Based Advertising

We also work with and permit certain third parties, including, but not limited to advertising networks and website analysis firms, to place cookies on your computer or browser when you view, click or otherwise interact with advertisements that are featured on our website. These third party cookies and analogous technology are used to gather non-personally identifiable information about your activities on our website and third party sites you may visit to serve you with advertisements that are relevant to your interests and preferences while you are on third party sites. Some of these third parties participate in the Digital Advertising Alliance (“DAA”), an industry self-regulatory program to give consumers a better understanding of and greater control over ads that are customized based on their online behavior across different web sites. To learn more and make choices about preference-based ads from participating third parties, please visit the DAA website at www.aboutads.info.

##### Updates to this Privacy Policy

We may update or change this Policy from time to time, with or without any advance notice. The date of the last change or update to this Policy shall be noted at the end of this Policy, and any changes made will be effective upon posting of the revised version. If there are material changes in the way we handle your personally-identifiable information, or to the Policy itself, including changes to the Preference Based Advertising practices set forth above, we will notify you using direct means, at our discretion – either through displaying a notice on our website or by sending you an email, so that you may review the changed terms and consent to them prior to continuing to use our website. We encourage you to check this policy whenever you use our website and services to understand how your personal information is used.
